porneq.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy

This document details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User Data collected on Porneq.com

The security of your Data is very important to Porneq.com and as such we take all appropriate steps to limit the risk that it may be lost, damaged or misused.

**This site expressly and strictly limits its membership and/or viewing privileges to adults 21 years of age and over or having attained the age of majority in their community.** All persons who do not meet its criteria are strictly forbidden from accessing or viewing the contents of this Site. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who have not attained the age of majority.

**DATA COLLECTED**

Personal Information:  
Non-Registered users can watch videos without registering and without any information being collected and processed. However the visitor's IP address will be recorded in the event that there is any misappropriation of information and/or content.  
Registered Members: Registration is required for uploading videos, and accessing a number of other features. The following personal information is requested at the time of registration: username (required), and email address (required). Additional personal information, such as year of birth, relationship status and sexual orientation may be added on a voluntary basis after registration, for members interested in identifying and potentially contacting other members meeting specific criteria. All this data with the exception of the email address and IP address becomes publicly accessible information.  
Content Uploaded to the site: Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.  
Cookies: When you visit Porneq.com, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser session. If you remove your cookies, some of the site's features may not function properly.  
Log File Information: When you visit Porneq.com, our servers may automatically record certain information that your web browser sends such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, platform type, domain names and the date and time of your request.  
Emails: If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

**USES**

Your Personally identifiable information submitted to Porneq.com is used to provide to the user the website's features and special personalized features.  
Your chosen username (not your email address) is displayed to other Users alongside the content you upload, including videos, comments, etc.  
Any videos that you submit to Porneq.com may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.  
We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent.  
We may use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of key website changes or for customer service purposes).  
We analyze aggregated user traffic information to help streamline our marketing and hosting operations and to improve the quality of the Porneq.com user-experience.

**DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

if under duty to do so Porneq.com may release data to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce our Terms Of Service and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of Porneq.com or our subscribers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations including the police and governmental authorities for the purposes of protection against fraud or any other kind of illegal activity whether or not identified in the Terms Of Service. It is Porneq.com's policy, whenever possible and legally permissible, to promptly notify you upon an obligation to supply data to any third party.  
Should you deliberately upload any illegal material Porneq.com shall forward all available information to all relevant authorities and this without notice.  
\- We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

**SECURITY**

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen a password) which enables you to access certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Porneq.com uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Porneq.com and you do so at your own risk.

**YOUR RIGHTS**

You are entitled to access and correct your Data by doing so directly on the website or by requesting us to do so via the Contact us section.

**GOOGLE ANALYTICS**

This website uses [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/), a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. For more information please visit "[Google Privacy Policies](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)"

**COOKIES**

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. We may use cookies in order to customize this site for visitors. These cookies are not required to browse the website. Additionally, third-party widgets such as Facebook may install cookies depending on their configuration. You are not required to accept any cookies to use this site. **We do not make any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any personally identifying information from any source.**
